Nitay Yacobovitch

054-6692505



https://nitayya.github.io/Nitay/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/nitayya/



nitayya@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Information Systems Management (Ben-Gurion University) Graduate

Detail-Oriented, team player, fast learner, passionate and dedicated to learn new skills

Knowledge in BI Concepts - DWH and ETL, experience and knowledge with BI Tools: SQL, Tableau, Power-BI,

Talend, EXCEL (VBA), Python libraries (Pandas, seaborn)

Experience and knowledge with: Java, C#

Experience and knowledge with WEB Tools: HTML, CSS, PHP, JS

CAREER

2020 - 2021

BI ANALYST

Sagarmatha

- Working with a US based retailer, to target personalized coupons within their loyalty program, while:
 - Setup, calibrate, execute and monitor the personalization engine (Sagarmatha's propriety software)
 - Querying from various large & complex data sets (SQL Server, Exasol), detect patterns based on shopper's behaviour to improve campaign performance and make data-driven decision making
 - Work closely within a team of Data analysts and BI developers to define ETL processes and analytic reports
 - Responsibility for all on-going operation activities, while working with oversea customers and customer success team

2018 - PRESENT

"Atomchip Group" in BGU's Physics department

ADMINISTRATIVE ROLE

- Management of the team's purchases and budget
- Management of contact with different role-players in BGU (in charge of purchases, budget, research & administration)
- for team members traveling abroad and their international guests
- General logistical management of team's activity

EDUCATION

2017 - 2020

BEN-GURION UNIVERSITY

Information Systems Management

- Final project at University's Internal audit office with Sharepoint
- Main courses: OOP, BI, WEB, CRM, Databases, IT Infrastructure Algorithms and Complexity

2015

WINGATE INSTITUTE

Basketball Coaches Course

MILITARY SERVICE

2012 - 2015

IDF

- Combat soldier on IDF's paratroopers Brigade (gun-authorization level 07)
- Driver for colonel on Ground Operations Command